(Penny:)But also how incredibly
happy you make me.
(Penny:)Thank you for marrying me.
(Penny:)Hopefully for the last time.
(Sceme:)Penny...
(Leonard:)as a scientist, my job is to
figure out why things happen.
(Leonard:)But I don't think
I'll ever understand
(Leonard:)how someone like me could get
to be with someone like you.
(Leonard:)You know... maybe... I don't
need to understand it,
I just need to be grateful.
I love you, Penny.
(Penny:)Oh...
(Bernadette:)Anybody have anything snarky
to say about that?
(Bernadette:)Didn't think so.
(Alfred:)I'd like to say something.
(Alfred:)Beverly, I know that
we don't bring out
(Alfred:)the best in each other.
But something wonderful did
come from our relationship:
that young man right there.
(Beverley:)I couldn't agree more.